Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Born-Digital Photographs, 1999-2019
  - Unsorted University photographs, 1999-2004
    - Michael DeLor, member of the class of 2005 masters..., 2003 August 28
    - Jarad Pennisi, member of the class of 2005 masters..., 2003 August 28
    - Panayiotis Ttiniozou, member of the class of 2005..., 2003 August 28
    - Members of the ambulance service at the University..., 2003 September 12
    - Madeleine Kunin, Diplomat and Politician, gives..., 2003 September 18
    - Karen DeWitt, Capital Bureau Chief, New York State..., 2003 September 18
    - Judtih Saidel addresses the guests at the..., 2003 September 18
    - Judtih Saidel addresses the guests at the..., 2003 September 18
    - Margaret Krause, chair of the board of directors..., 2003 September 18
    - Donna Bellino (class of 2004) stands in the State..., 2004 January 13
    - The audience at the seventh annual New York State..., 2003 January 14
    - New York State assemblyman Richard Gottfried..., 2003 January 14
    - An unidentified person at Dr. Shahedipour-..., 2003 January 16
    - Dr. Shahedipour-Sandvik's lab at the University at..., 2003 January 16
    - The University at Albany's pep band rehearses in..., 2004 January 21
    - The University at Albany's pep band rehearses in..., 2004 January 21
    - The University at Albany's pep band rehearses in..., 2004 January 21
    - The University at Albany's pep band rehearses in..., 2004 January 21
    - New York State Senator Joseph Bruno shaking hands..., 2003 January 28
    - An unidentified woman; Tamas Bodor, professor; and..., 2004 January 28
    - Left to right, Dr. John Collins, an executive of..., 2003 January 31
    - Distinguished Service Professor Timothy Lance,..., 2002 October 1
    - Professor of English Martha Rozett stands near..., 2002 October 1
    - Distinguished Professor Terence Thornberry of the..., 2002 October 1
    - University at Albany alumna Catherine Bertini,..., 2003 October 10
    - Provost and Vice President for Academic Affairs..., 2002 October 21
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 October 21
    - Times Union Publisher George R. Hearst III of the..., 2002 October 21
    - Target Corporation team members (in red) presents..., 2003 October 22
    - Unidentified individuals enjoy the reception..., 2002 October 25
    - An unidentified person works on a computer inside..., 2002 October 25
    - Unidentified persons perform onstage at the..., 2002 October 25
    - Unidentified persons perform onstage at the..., 2002 October 25
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 October 28
    - Unidentified persons at a reception for the Center..., 2002 October 28
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 October 28
    - Paulette J. McCormick, Ph.D. and University at..., 2002 October 28
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 October 28
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 October 28
    - An unidentified person speaking at the 15th..., 2002 October 29
    - Individuals posing at the 15th National Renewable..., 2002 October 29
    - An unidentified man, speaking during a press..., 2003 October 29
    - Unidentified persons at a University at Albany..., 2002 October 3
    - Findlay Cockrell, Professor Emeritus at the..., 2003 October 30
    - Michael Messitt, Director & Assistant Dean of the..., 2003 October 30
    - From left to right, an unidentified man, Ted..., 2003 October 30
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 October 30
    - University at Albany students take part in the..., 2004 October 8
    - A group of individuals, including William Kennedy..., 2003 November 10
    - Craig DeVoe, Account Executive, Apple, speaks at..., 2003 November 10
    - Craig DeVoe, Regional Educational Representative..., 2003 November 10
    - Actors perform at a press conference for the..., 2003 November 10
    - University at Albany Rockefeller College of Public..., 2002 November 13
    - University at Albany Faculty Michele Przedwiecki..., 2002 November 13
    - Professor Marcia Sutherland of the University at..., 2002 November 19
    - Unidentified persons, cheerleaders and an event..., 2002 November 20
    - Unidentified students in the auditorium at the..., 2002 November 20
    - Taping of MSNBC's Hardball with Chris Matthews at..., 2002 November 20
    - Host Chris Matthews preparing for the taping of..., 2002 November 20
    - Host Chris Matthews preparing for the taping of..., 2002 November 20
    - An unidentified person holds the United States..., 2002 November 20
    - Hillary Rodham Clinton after the taping of MSNBC's..., 2002 November 20
    - (From the left) University at Albany Professor of..., 2003 November 20
    - New York State Governor George Pataki, University..., 2002 November 21
    - President and CEO of Tokyo Electron Limited..., 2002 November 21
    - Tisha Lewis hosting "The Healing Room" radio show..., 2002 November 26
    - Unidentified member of the 2002-2003 University at..., 2002 November 5
    - The 2002-2003 University at Albany women's..., 2002 November 5
    - Richard Feldman of the Delmar Reformed Church..., 2003 December 1
    - New York Senator Charles Schumer speaks at the..., 2002 December 12
    - An unidentified man attends a press conference at..., 2003 December 15
    - Michael R. McNulty, New York State Congressman and..., 2003 December 15
    - New York Assemblyman and chairman of the Energy..., 2003 December 15
    - Corporal Andre Williams, class of 2003, presents..., 2003 December 5
    - The crowd supports the players at a University at..., 2003 December 5
    - Both of the University at Albany's mascots, Lil' D..., 2003 December 5
    - Freshman Courtney Johnson of the University at..., 2003 December 5
    - An unidentified man attends the Energy and..., 2004 February 10
    - Unidentified persons pose together in the lab at..., 2003 February 11
    - Professor of Biological Sciences Dr. John T...., 2003 February 11
    - Frank Thompson, dean of Rockefeller College of..., 2004 February 11
    - Group photograph of attendees from the retirement..., 2004 February 11
    - Individuals attend the University at Albany's..., 2004 February 12
    - Carlos Santiago, officer in charge and provost,..., 2004 February 12
    - Three unidentified persons work on a jigsaw puzzle..., 2002 February 21
    - Unidentified person affiliated with the School of..., 1999 February 25
    - Unidentified person speaking to six unidentified..., 1999 February 25
    - Undergraduate business administration students are..., 2004 February 25
    - Unidentified person, from portraits of Group Tour..., 2002 February 5
    - Lynne Allard and Anne Hobday pose at the 2002..., 2002 February 6
    - Paul Stee, University at Albany President Karen..., 2002 February 6
    - Visitors enjoy the grand opening of Ritazza's, a..., 2000
    - Students take a few minutes to chat at the grand..., 2000
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock,..., 2000
    - Edward Mayer, Professor and Sculpture Area Head,..., 2000
    - University at Albany alumni discuss a veteran's..., 2000
    - University at Albany alumni discuss a veteran's..., 2000
    - Members of the University at Albany community wait..., 2000
    - The third-place runner crosses the finish line in..., 2000
    - DJs from radio station Fly 92 officiate at the..., 2000
    - An unidentified keynote speaker addresses the..., 2000
    - Dick Highfield speaks at a breakfast event for the..., 2000
    - Visitors view exhibits at the Professional..., 2000
    - Michael Dye (center) of the Best Western Sovereign..., 2000
    - Scott Stryker (center) of OfficeTeam receives a..., 2000
    - Unidentified guests view a technology bulletin..., 2000
    - A competitor receives encouragement in the Russian..., 2000
    - Faculty of the Department of Women's Studies at..., 2000
    - Unidentified members of the University at Albany..., 2001
    - John Ashbery addresses the audience after..., 2001
    - Musicians are under the watchful eye of their..., 2001
    - Musicians in the string section rehearse for an..., 2001
    - Unidentified men discuss new technology at the..., 2001
    - Unidentified men discuss new technology at the..., 2001
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2001
    - A math professor teaches a class for the..., 2001
    - An unidentified woman from the Educational..., 2001
    - Students from the Educational Opportunity Program..., 2001
    - Professor Gloria Ladson-Billings of the University..., 2001
    - Roslyn Jefferson, Employee Assistance Coordinator..., 2001
    - Unidentified woman participates in discussion with..., 2001
    - Kangwon National University President Yong Soo..., 2001
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock and..., 2001
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2001
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2001
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2001
    - Congressman and civil rights leader John Lewis..., 2001
    - Congressman and civil rights leader John Lewis..., 2001
    - Professor Grace Mose of the Women's Studies..., 2001
    - An unidentified speaker addresses the audience at..., 2001
    - An unidentified speaker addresses the audience at..., 2001
    - Colleagues enjoy the 25th anniversary reception..., 2001
    - Members of the University at Albany's Professional..., 2001
    - Members of the University at Albany's Professional..., 2001
    - Actor George Plimpton talks with a guest at a..., 2001
    - A soldier marches into the University at Albany..., 2001
    - The honor guard prepares to lead participants off..., 2001
    - The University at Albany community closes a Unity..., 2001
    - An unidentified University at Albany student who..., 2001
    - David Wills, chair of the Department of Languages,..., 2001
    - Unidentified persons speaking at the New York..., 2002
    - Unidentified persons speaking at the New York..., 2002
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002
    - V. Mark Durand, Department of Psychology,..., 2002 March 11
    - V. Mark Durand, Department of Psychology,..., 2002 March 11
    - An unidentified man speaks at the dedication..., 2004 March 11
    - Unidentified persons participating in the Annual..., 2002 March 12
    - Unidentified person speaking to students during..., 2002 March 12
    - Newly appointed University at Albany interim..., 2004 March 12
    - Audience members attend the welcome reception of..., 2004 March 12
    - Newly appointed University at Albany interim..., 2004 March 12
    - Will Brown speaks while an unidentified person..., 2002 March 13
    - Henry Louis Taylor, Jr., keynote speaker and..., 2002 March 14
    - Unidentified persons seated in the audience at a..., 2003 March 19
    - Unidentified persons at the recpetion following a..., 2003 March 19
    - A University at Albany singing group at a peace..., 2003 March 24
    - The audience seated outside at a peace vigil for..., 2003 March 24
    - Unidentified high school students tour the..., 2003 March 27
    - Bob Gluck, assistant professor of music and..., 2004 March 3
    - Photo of Jordan Edelson, undergraduate student at..., 2004 March 3
    - University at Albany student, Peter Brusoe, Class..., 2004 March 31
    - Donald Faulkner and unidentified persons at an..., 2002 March 4
    - Kenneth Jackson during his lecture "The End of..., 2002 March 4
    - Kenneth Jackson during his lecture "The End of..., 2002 March 4
    - William Kennedy (left), Ivan Steen (right) at..., 2002 March 4
    - Left to right Don Faulkner, director of the New..., 2004 March 4
    - Unidentified persons speaking at a booth for the..., 2002 March 6
    - Unidentified persons shaking hands at a booth at..., 2002 March 6
    - Unidentified persons working for the Annual Fund..., 2002 April 1
    - Unidentified person making a phone call for the..., 2002 April 1
    - Unidentified person making a phone call for the..., 2002 April 1
    - University at Albany students in the East Asian..., 2004 April 1
    - Unidentified persons at a celebration of the 350th..., 2002 April 10
    - Philanthropists Matthew and Phoebe Bender pose..., 2002 April 10
    - University at Albany President Karen Hithcock..., 2002 April 11
    - University at Albany School of Business Dean..., 2002 April 11
    - MIT professor, physicist, and Noble Prize..., 2002 April 19
    - MIT professor, physicist, and Noble Prize..., 2002 April 19
    - MIT professor, physicist, and Noble Prize..., 2002 April 19
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 19
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock and..., 2002 April 22
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 22
    - Antonia Coello Novello, New York State..., 2002 April 22
    - University at Albany students at an University at..., 2002 April 22
    - Carlos Santiago, University at Albany officer in..., 2004 April 28
    - A unidentified faculty member from the University..., 2004 April 29
    - Albany Mayor Jerry Jennings speaking at the press..., 2002 April 3
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 3
    - Alain Kaloyeros, Dean of the School of..., 2002 April 30
    - Alain Kaloyeros, Dean of the School of..., 2002 April 30
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 30
    - Frances George, Edward George and Sorrell Chesin..., 2002 April 30
    - John Ryan (left) and University at Albany interim..., 2004 April 30
    - Peter Levin, dean of the School of Public Health,..., 2004 April 30
    - University at Albany Interim President John Ryan..., 2004 April 30
    - The University at Albany unveiled its Storm Ready..., 2004 April 30
    - Christine Haile, University at Albany Chief..., 2002 April 4
    - U.S. EPA Administrator Christie Whitman during a..., 2002 April 5
    - Administrator of the EPA Christine Whitman during..., 2002 April 5
    - Two unidentified persons at the University at..., 1999 April 9
    - Two unidentified persons at the University at..., 1999 April 9
    - Unidentified persons at the University at Albany's..., 1999 April 9
    - Associate Vice President for Academic Affair sat..., 2003 April 9
    - From left, Alan Hevesi, New York State Comptroller..., 2004 May 13
    - Jeryl Mumpower, professor at the Rockefeller..., 2004 May 13
    - Unidentified students and faculty in the..., 2003 May 14
    - Lynn Gilmore Canton shaking hands with an..., 2003 May 15
    - Unidentified faculty members preparing for the..., 2003 May 15
    - John Cahill, Secretary and Governor George..., 2003 May 15
    - John Nielson and unidentified people following the..., 2003 May 15
    - Catherine Bertini and New York State Assemblyman..., 2002 May 16
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 May 16
    - Catherine Bertini speaking at the podium of at the..., 2002 May 16
    - Katharine Briar-Lawson, Dean & Professor School of..., 2002 May 16
    - New York State Assemblyman Richard Brodsky,..., 2002 May 16
    - Catherine Bertini and unidentified person pose at..., 2002 May 16
    - Philip Eppard and V. Chapman-Smith attending the..., 2002 May 16
    - Unidentified members of the University at Albany's..., 2003 May 16
    - An unidentified University at Albany student and..., 2004 May 16
    - The 2004 undergraduate departmental graduation..., 2004 May 16
    - Larry Pasti speaks at a community forum on place..., 2004 May 18
    - Lee McElroy Jr. (left), University at Albany..., 2004 May 3
    - Lee McElroy Jr. (left), University at Albany..., 2004 May 3
    - Lee McElroy Jr. (left), University at Albany..., 2004 May 3
    - Distinguished Service Professor Shirley Jones, of..., 2004 May 3
    - An unidentified person speakingat the Great Dane..., 2003 May 5
    - University at Albany Basketball Coach Will Brown..., 2003 May 5
    - Two unidentified persons pose at the Great Dane..., 2003 May 5
    - Head Coach of Men's Lacrosse Scott Marr and an..., 2003 May 5
    - Emil Bove and Theresa Masse posing with 2002-2003..., 2003 May 5
    - University at Albany students participate in the..., 2004 May 5
    - University at Albany Professor Sophia Lubensky's..., 2003 May 6
    - Jack Knowlton (right), co-owner of the 2003..., 2004 May 6
    - An unidentified man speaks at an event honoring..., 2004 May 6
    - Outgoing University at Albany President Karen..., 2004 May 7
    - Sue Faerman, dean of undergraduate education,..., 2004 May 7
    - Helen Desfosses, associate professor of Public..., 2004 May 7
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 May 9
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 May 9
    - School of Business Dean Richard Highfield,..., 2003 June 11
    - School of Business Dean Richard Highfield,..., 2003 June 11
    - An unidentified person speaking at the podium at..., 2003 June 11
    - University at Albany's Dean and Professor of the..., 2003 June 11
    - M.F.A. student Chris Cassidy working on a piece of..., 2003 June 17
    - David '53 and Frances Martin '71 speak to..., 2002 June 20
    - Professor Karla Goldman speaking at the Conference..., 2002 June 20
    - New York State Governor George E. Pataki speaks at..., 2004 June 22
    - New York State Senator Joseph Bruno shaking hands..., 2003 June 24
    - New York State Senator Joseph Bruno uses an..., 2003 June 24
    - New York State Senator Joseph Bruno poses with..., 2003 June 24
    - Unidentified persons seated at an event sponsored..., 2003 June 3
    - University at Albany Libraries Director Meredith..., 2003 June 3
    - Steven and Arlene Mirer (seated) with Martin..., 2003 June 3
    - Professor of Judaic Studies Mark Raider stands..., 2003 June 3
    - Architect Benjamin Mendel, Jr., Ruth Mendel, and..., 2003 June 3
    - University at Albany Provost and Vice President..., 2003 June 3
    - A group of alumni attend 2004 Alumni Weekend..., 2004 June 4
    - Dr. Joseph Bowman of the Center for Urban Youth..., 2002 June 5
    - An unidentified person seated at a meeting of the..., 2003 June 9
    - University at Albany School of Social Welfare..., 2003 June 9
    - "Before" pictures of a dorm room in the State Quad..., 2002 July 17
    - "Before" pictures of a dorm room in the State Quad..., 2002 July 17
    - New York Senator Joseph Bruno, New York State..., 2002 July 18
    - New York State Governor George Pataki speaks to..., 2002 July 18
    - Dean of the School of Nanosciences and..., 2002 July 18
    - Employees of the University at Albany's Public..., 2002 July 23
    - Helen Desfosses speaking at Media Day for the New..., 2002 July 24
    - New York Giants Head Football Coach Jim Fassel..., 2002 July 24
    - Bishop David J. Bena shakes hands with WNYT NBC 13..., 2003 July 25
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 July 25
    - Albany County Legislator Michael Breslin, New York..., 2002 July 26
    - Chancellor of the State University of New York..., 2003 July 29
    - Chancellor of the State University of New York..., 2003 July 29
    - A side view of one of the 10 new Global Electric..., 2003 July 29
    - Department of Art professor Edward Mayer and..., 2002 August 27
    - Musa Aghamirzayev, member of the class of 2005..., 2003 August 28
    - An unidentified member of the class of 2005..., 2003 August 28
    - Daniel Dugan, member of the class of 2005 masters..., 2003 August 28
    - Christine Galka, member of the class of 2005..., 2003 August 28
    - Shih Yun Huang, member of the class of 2005..., 2003 August 28
    - Michael Maskallis, member of the class of 2005..., 2003 August 28
    - Terry Thomas, member of the class of 2005 masters..., 2003 August 28
    - Jay Werther, member of the class of 2005 masters..., 2003 August 28
    - Helen Desfosses addresses the University at..., 2003 September 18
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 September 18
    - Maud Easter, director of "Voices for Change,..., 2003 September 18
    - Dr. Anne Elliott, executive director of Project..., 2003 September 18
    - New York State Senator Joseph Bruno stands at the..., 2002 September 19
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock is..., 2000 September 15
    - New York State assemblyman Richard Gottfried..., 2003 January 14
    - New York State assemblyman Richard Gottfried..., 2003 January 14
    - Sarah Decker (class of 2004), recipient of the..., 2004 January 15
    - Associate Professor of Nanoengineering Dr. Fatemeh..., 2003 January 16
    - Unidentified persons at a presentation on Case..., 2002 January 18
    - Melanie Trimble, executive director of NYCLU..., 2004 January 22
    - Melanie Trimble, executive director of NYCLU..., 2004 January 22
    - Dean of the School of Nanosciences and..., 2003 January 28
    - An unidentified woman; Sharon Dawes, senior..., 2004 January 28
    - Frank Thompson, dean of the Rockefeller College of..., 2004 January 28
    - Left to right, Alden Doolittle, director of..., 2003 January 31
    - Distinguished Professor Judith Langer, of the..., 2002 October 1
    - An unidentified person stands near University at..., 2002 October 1
    - Distinguished Professor of Social Welfare Jan..., 2002 October 1
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 October 21
    - Cyprus's ambassador to the United States Erato..., 2002 October 21
    - An unidentified person at a document signing..., 2002 October 21
    - Times Union Publisher George R. Hearst III shaking..., 2002 October 21
    - Times Union Publisher George R. Hearst III of the..., 2002 October 21
    - Individuals walk through the interior of the..., 2002 October 25
    - College of Arts and Sciences Dean Joan Wick-..., 2002 October 25
    - Professor John Pipkin addresses an audience at the..., 2002 October 25
    - An unidentified person speaks at the dedication..., 2002 October 25
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 October 28
    - Al Millis, Ph.D. and an unidentified person at a..., 2002 October 28
    - Jeryl Mumpower and unidentified faculty member..., 2003 October 28
    - Linda Trocki speaking at the podium at the 15th..., 2002 October 29
    - An unidentified person speaking at the 15th..., 2002 October 29
    - An unidentified person presenting a slideshow at..., 2002 October 29
    - The University at Albany hosts "The Kennedy Papers..., 2003 October 29
    - Author William Kennedy and University at Buffalo..., 2003 October 29
    - The University at Albany Head of Special..., 2003 October 29
    - From left to right, Mary Johnson, Marissa Berley,..., 2003 October 30
    - Warren Bagatelle, Class of 1960, and Bernard D...., 2003 October 30
    - Leo McElory, Vice President for Athletic..., 2003 October 30
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock and..., 2003 October 30
    - Unidentified particiapnts in the University at..., 2003 October 31
    - The University at Albany's Kids Growing Food (KGF)..., 2003 October 7
    - The University at Albany's Kids Growing Food (KGF)..., 2003 October 7
    - University at Albany students take part in the..., 2004 October 8
    - University at Albany students take part in the..., 2004 October 8
    - Attendees visit stations at an event for the..., 2003 November 10
    - William Kennedy, Pulitzer Prize-winning author and..., 2003 November 10
    - University at Albany President, Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 November 10
    - University at Albany Faculty Michele Przedwiecki..., 2002 November 13